Guide to the Donald Kennedy Personal Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2009-139
  - Welcome to Freshmen September 20, 1984 (#198) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Parents Day Convocation 9-20-1984 (#198) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Inauguration Address 10-1-1984 University of Rochester (#200) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - "Alumni Talk: the Undergraduate" October 1984 (#201) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Public Service Reception 10/10/84 (#202) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Med Center 25th Anniversary 10/12/84 (#203) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Monterey Bay Aquarium Dedication 10/20/84 (#204) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - McClatchy Dedication 10-17-1984 (#205) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Senior Coordinating Council 10-17-1984 (#206) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Junior Convocation 10-19-1984 (#207) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Assoc. of Colleges and Universities of New York 11/1/84 (#208) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - "BC Big Game Thing" 11/8/84 (#209) (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Seminar on Civic Learning 11/12/84 (#210) (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Richter Inauguration 11/14/84 (#211) (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Public Management Program Seminar "Managm't in Gov't & the Academy" 12/4/84 (#212) (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - "The Rebirth of Obligation" 12/7/84 Opportunities Industrialization Center (#213) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Cardinal Club Auction 11/16/85 (#211A) (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Toast at Lee Annenberg Dinner 12/26/84 (#214) (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Arizona Centennial 1/12/84 (#215) (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Univ. of Arizona Centennial 1/12/85 (#215) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Centennial Inauguration Welcome 3/9/85 (#216) (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Founder's Day Remarks 1985 (#216A) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - L.A. Alumni Conference 3/16/85 (#217) (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Background on L.A. Conference Speech March 16, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - "Role of the Research University" Symposium on Economics and Technology 3/18/85 (#218) (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Physics Symposium honoring Robert Hofstadter 3/23/85 (#219) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Science & "Other" Cultures – Palo Alto Senior Center 3/25/85 (#220) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Medicine & the University remarks – Commtt on Med & Humanities 4/4/85 (#221) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Hunger Conference Rally Introduction 4/8/85 (#222) (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Thacher School Centennial April 13, 1985 (#223) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Thacher School Centennial 4/13/85 (#223) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Divestment – Rally Remarks 4/25/85 (#224) (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Divestment – Forum Remarks SOSA-Brd of Trustees 5/7/85 (#225) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Rotary Club International 4/26/85 (#226) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Alumni Conference Remarks 5/11/85 – Bowman, see 99, 148 (notes only) (#227) (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Report to the Academic Council, Spring '85 5/16/85 (#228) (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Third World – Our Challenges – (notes) – Overseas Development Symposium 5/18/85 (#229) (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - CIS Dedication (notes) (#230) (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Commencement – 1985: Welcome, Farewell to Grads (#231) (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Commencement '85 – Cuomo (#231) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - S-635 Anti-Apartheid Act Senate Banking Committee 5/23/85 (#232) (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Notes--51st Mtg Advisory Committee to Director, NIH 6/27/85 (#233) (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Sterling Memorial – William Sterling Remarks 7/9/85 (#234) (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Sterling Memorial Services (#234) (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Education: How Much Do We Really Need It? 7/16/85 (#235) (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Commonwealth Club North – Anchorage, Alaska 7/16/85 (#235) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Inter. Assoc. of Universities 8/12/85 – UCLA (#236) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Paying for College – Rotary Club – Canada College 8/85 (#237) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Orientation Week, 1985; see 41, 83, 198, 200 (#238) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Parent's Day 9/19/85 (#239) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Private Schools, Public Choices 10/4/85 (#240) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dublin, NH – 10/5/85 – "Private Schools, Public Choices" (#240) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Advice for Gov't that Didn't Ask 10/3/85 (#241) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Advice for Gov't that Didn't Ask – San Diego Rotary 10/1985 (#241) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Junior Convocation 9/27/85 (#242) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Mills College Greeting 10/11/85 (#243) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Parent's Day 10/25/85 (#246) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Macalaster College – St. Paul, MN – "Education in the 21st Century" 10/30/85 (#247) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Education in the 21st Century 10/30/85 (#247) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Palo Alto Area YMCA Dinner 10/29/85 (#248) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Sempervirens Fundraising Dinner – notes 11/4/85 (#248A) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - We're Sacrificing Youth on Mediocrity's Altar" 11/3/85, Sacramento Bee (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Big Game Night – Bohemian Club SF 11/14/85 (#249) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Cent. – Convocation – Open. Remarks & Intro, Frank Rhodes 11/11/85 (#250) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - ASSU (Senate) Forum – Public Service & Activism 11/11/85 (#250A) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Urban Coalition 11/21/85 (#251) (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Pre-Campaign Meeting Remarks "Stanford Today" 11/21/85 (#252) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Gov't Investment: Why Can't We Prepare for the Future 12/5/85 (#253) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Monterey – Calif. State Demo Caucus – "Gov't Investment: Why Can't We…" 12/5/85 (#253) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Wash. DC – Food & Drug Law Insti. 12/9/85 (#254) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Wash. DC – Testimony – Sub. Of Employment Opportunity, House of Representatives 10/85 (#254A) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Farewell Dinner – Larry Crowley – Faculty Club 12/10/85 (#255) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - "Hospital Governance" – FCPM 279 Class (Merchant Class, SUH) 1/16/86 (#255A) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - SU – Bishop Tutu, Intro. 1/21/86 (#256) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Hometel Groundbreaking – SUMC 1/22/86 (#257) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Sacto. CA – Rotary Club "Can We Help…" 3/20/86 (#258) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - "Can We Help…" Washington, DC 3/12/86 (#258) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Can We Help? Public Service & the Young 4/15/86 (#258A&B) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - SF, Rotary Club – Can We Help?..." 4/15/86 (#258) (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - LA – Alum Symposium – "How Can We Look So Rich, Yet Feel So Poor?" 3/16/86 (#259) (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - SU – Taube-Baron Collection for Jewish Studies 4/13/86 (#260) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - SF Univ. High School – "Excellence in Secondary Education" 4/16/86 (#261) (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Las Vegas – West. Assoc. of College… Business Off. 4/28/86 (#261A) (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - SU – Academic Council – Faculty Benefits 5/1/86 (#262) (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Faculty Benefits 5/1/86 (#262) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - S. Diego – Carnegie Forum, Notes. Panel, "Reflections on Meeting" 5/17/86 (#263) (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Bev. Hills – Tyler Prize Award 5/17/86 (#264) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Sacto. AICCU Testimony - …Master Plan for Higher Ed. 5/21/86 (#265) (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Kansas City – Midwest Research Insti. 5/22/86 (#266) (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Class Day 6/14/86 (#267) (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Introduction to Ted Koppel 6/15/86 (#268A) (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Ted Koppel's Speech 6/15/86 (#268B) (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Commencement 1986 – Farewell to Graduates 6/15/86 (#268) (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Bohemian Grove Speech – "Investing in the Young" 7/18/86 (#269) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Investing in the Young 7/18/86 (#269) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Nature Conservancy – Ring Mtg. 7/19/86 (#270) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Kenya Notes (notes only) 8/86 (#270B) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Anniversaries & Institutional Renewal – Reed College 9/18/86 (#271) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Welcome to Freshmen – Orientation Week 9/25/86 (#272) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Junior Convocation 10/3/86 (#273) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - University Fellows 10/13/86 (#274) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Volunteers 10/16/86 (#275) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - NYAS: The Investment Crisis in American Science – NY 10/23/86 (#276) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Centennial – Statement of Opportunity & Purposes 11/86 (#277) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Sterling Circle Dinner – LA 11/7/86 (#278) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Senate – Exploring Educational Initiatives for South African Blacks 11/13/86 (#279) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Myth of the Cutting Edge SCAP – Pasadena 11/19/86 (#280) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Area I Requirement – Academic Council 11/20/86 (#281) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Derek Bok Introduction 12/11/86 (#282) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - You Can Make A Difference 1/31/87 (#283) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Excellence in People (Greenbrier) 2/1/87 (#284) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Conference Board Cont. Council Palm Springs 2/3/87 (#285) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Allan Cox Memorial 2/3/87 (#286) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Media Press Conference 2/4/87 (#287) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Media Luncheon (NYC) 2/6/87 (#288) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - The Public & the University – LA 2/17/87 (#289) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Introduction of Jimmy Carter 3/10/87 (#290) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - New Childrens' Hospital Remarks 3/24/87 (#291) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Ronald Reagan Library Remarks Faculty Senate 4/2/87 (#292) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Introduction of Dr. Roy Anderson – DSJordan Award 4/13/87 (#293) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Our Universities: Investing in Whose Interest? 4/17/87 (#294) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Helping Innovation PA Rotary 4/20/87 (#294A) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Remarks to ASSU Senate 4/21/87 (#295) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Opening Remarks/Humanities Center 4/23/87 (#296) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Conservation Strategies 4/24/87 (#297) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Conservation Strategies (outline) 4/24/87 (#297) (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Cent. Campaign Remarks – Donor Breakfast 5/14/87 (#297A) (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Cornerstone Welcome – DK 5/14/87 (#298A) (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Welcome by W. Christopher 5/14/87 (#298B) (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - C. George Shultz Cornerstone Address 5/14/87 (#298C) (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - SU – Cornerstone Centennial – Campus Report 5/20/87 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Cornerstone Weekend Alumni Talk 5/16/87 (#299) (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Annual Fund Volunteer Conference Outline – Intro of D. Feinstein 5/15/87 (#300) (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - The Universities: Fostering Innovation 5/20/87 (#301) (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - The Universities: Fostering Innovation 5/20/87 (#301) (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Derek Bok Comments (outline) 5/20/87 (#301A) (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Forum on Racism Introduction 5/26/87 (#302) (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - R.L. Stevenson Commencement 5/29/87 (#303) (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Commencement '87 Welcome-DK (#304A) (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Commencement '87 Farewell to Graduates-DK (#304B) (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Commencement '87 Introduction to Tip O'Neill (#304C) (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Commencement '87 Tip O'Neill's Speech (#304D) (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Times-Mirror Talk (outline) LA 6/16/87 (#305) (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Student Pugwash Remarks – notes 6/30/87 (#306) (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - ‘On Relations between University & Industry' AA/BoT 9/16/87 (#307) (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Parents' Day Convocation 9/25/87 see #239 (#308) (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Welcome to Transfers 9/25/87 (#309) (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Freshmen Welcome 9/25/87 (#310) (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Junior Convocation 10/2/87 (#311) (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Spring Hill Letter 10/5/87 (#312) (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Library's Place in Cent. Campaign LA 10/7/87 (#313) (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - NIH Centennial Keynote Address SF 10/9/87 (#314) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "Indirect Costs & Health of Universities" 10/16/87 (#315) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "Indirect Costs & Health of Universities" NIH 10/16/87 (#315) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Leadership & Innovation in Modern Society/Kennedy/Bok Event LA 10/20/87 (#316) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - "Providing for Leadership & Innovation in Modern Society" 10/20/87 (#316) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Derek Bok's Outline – Kennedy/Bok 10/20/87 (#316A) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Alcohol Forum Introduction 11/11/87 (#317) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Tully Friedman Luncheon (notes) SF 11/12/87 (#318) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Calif. School Board Assn. The Universities and the Schools 12/11/87 (#319) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Apple University 12/14/87 (#320) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - "Education: An Agenda for the Next Administration" 1/15/88 (#321) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Commonwealth Club – An Agenda for the Next Administration 1/15/88 (#321) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Genitourinary Surgeons – notes 2/26/88 (#324) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Amy Blue Presentation 1/17/88 (#322A) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Western Culture Remarks – Faculty Senate 1/21/88 (#323) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Amy Blue Memorial Services 5/21/88 (#322B) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Nat'l Centennial Celebration Friday Donor Dinner SF 3/4/88 (#325) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - NCC – Saturday Luncheon Remarks SF 3/5/88 (#326) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - How Come We Look So Big, Yet Feel So Small?" 3/6/88 (#327) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Look Big, Feel Small – LA AA Conf. 3/6/88 (#327) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - LA Times Luncheon Education Panel (notes) 3/16/88 (#328) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Levison Memorial Service 3/21/88 (#329) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Health & Safety Statement 3/29/88 (#330) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Ed Escobedo Eulogy 4/13/88 (#331) (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Long Range Planning Academic Council 4/14/88 (#332) (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Chinese for Affirmative Action Dinner 4/27/88 (#333) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Western Culture Remarks (notes) Los Angeles 4/29/88 (#334) (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - NCC Seattle Luncheon 5/7/88 (#335A) (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - NCC "Generic" Talk Spring '88 (#335B) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Campus Conference Remarks 5/14/88 (#336) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Stanford in Washington Dedication Press Club 3/16/88 (#337) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Otero Incident Remarks 5/25/88 (#338) (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Otero Incident Remarks – Senate 5/26/88 (#338) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Humans/Chemicals-Agricultural Issues Sacramento 6/2/88 (#339) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Commencement 1988 – Welcome 6/12/88 (#340A) (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Commencement 1988 – Farewell to Graduates 6/12/88 (#340B) (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Maynard Introduction 6/12/88 (#340C) (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Maynard Speech 6/12/88 (#340D) (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Guggenhime Memorial 7/12/88 (#341) (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Regulation of Science – Woods Hole 8/6/88 (#342) (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Ivy Talk 9/14/88 (3343) (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Parents' Day Welcome 9/22/88 see # 239 (#344) (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Freshmen Welcome '88 9/23/88 (#345) (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - South Bay Alumni Talk 9/27/88 (#346) (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Junior Convocation 9/28/88 (#347) (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Scenario 2010 Friday Noon Live 10/7/88 (#348) (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Academic Senate – Hoover 10/13/88 (#349) (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - .Accountability and Authorship: Where does the Responsibility Lie? 10/17/88 (#350) (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Accountability & Authorship: Biology Editors Talk WDC 10/17/88 (#350) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Council of Biology Editors 10/17/88 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Learning, Thinking, Believing NCC LA 11/6/88 (#351) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Learning, Thinking, Believing 11/6/88 (#351) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Israel Bond Dinner SF 11/6/88 (#352) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Uncommon Man – Cecil Green Dallas 11/15/88 (#353) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - CERAS Welcome 11/17/88 (#354) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Big Game Bonfire Rally 11/17/88 (#355) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Education Roundtable LA (notes) 12/1/88 (#356) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Senate – Sid Drell/ CISAC Resignation Remarks 12/1/88 (#357) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Index of Donald Kennedy's Speeches, #1-554 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Reflections on Racial Understanding Jan ‘89 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Commencement Welcome Boesak 1/12/89 (#358) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Science and the American Future 1/14/89 (#359) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Science and the American Future AAS 1/14/89 (#359) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - State of the University SF Alumni Association (notes) 1/18/89 (#360) (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - SU Palo Alto Growth Policies Leadership PA 1/20/89 (#361) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Fraud in Biomedical Sciences – Cell Biologists 1/30/89 (#361A) (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Intro of Geo. Shultz 2/8/89 (#362) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Freedom of Expression – Faculty Senate 2/9/89 (#363) (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - NCC – San Jose 2/11/89 (#364) (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - FDA Experience (notes) – Adams House 2/22/89 (#365) (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Marlborough School (draft) 2/25/89 (#366) (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - SUH Development Council (notes) 3/9/89 (#367) (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Founder's Day Remarks 3/12/89 (#368) (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Age Conference 3/31/89 (#369) (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Welcome Remarks – American College of Physicians 4/13/89 (#370) (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Choosing Medicine – Welcoming Remarks 4/13/88 (#370) (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Accountability – Friday Symposium (notes) 4/29/89 (#371) (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - International Security in the 21st Century 5/5/89 (#372) (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - NCC Portland 5/6/89 (#373) (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - International Security in the 21st Century – The Portland City Club 5/5/89 (#374) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Report to Academic Council 5/18/89 (#374) (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Harvard Grad School: 100th Anniversary 6/2/89 (#375) (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - CONA – Peace Meets the Environment Maine 6/3/89 (#376) (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Harvard Grad School – 100th Anniversary 6/2/89 (#375) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Remarks to University Fellows 6/13/89 (#376A) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Welcome (#377A) (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Garry Trudeau's Address (#377B) (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Commencement 1989 – DK Farewell to Graduates (#377A) (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Introduction of Gary Trudeau (#377C) (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Science Rich & Poor – Bus. Higher Ed Program 6/23/89 (#378) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Welcome International Conference on Materials & Mechanics of Superconductivity 7/24/89 (#379) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Sierra Camp Remarks (outline) 8/24/89 (#380) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Remarks to PA School District Personnel 8/31/89 (#381) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Remarks (notes) 9/12/89 (#382) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Greetings to Medical Students 9/19/89 see #82 (#383) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Students Convocation (notes) 9/89 (#383A) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Parents' Day Convocation 9/21/89 (#384) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Transfer Welcome 9/21/89 (#385) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Welcome to Freshmen 9/22/89 (#386) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Bill Chace Inauguration – Wesleyan 9/23/89 (#387) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Bill Chace Inaugural Remarks 9/23/89 (#387B) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Sophomore Celebration 9/26/89 (#388) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Junior Convocation 9/27/89 See #347 (#389) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - MDP (notes) 10/5/89 (#390) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Intro to Ralston Award, Brest/Arias 10/5/89 (#391) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - State of the University 10/7/89 (#392) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Welcome Remarks-Annual Review 10/21/89 (#392A) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Risk Analysis: Lessons from the War Zone 10/31/89 (#393) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Second UCMI Implementation Report 11/30/89 (#394) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - NCC-Friday (San Diego) 12/1/89 (#395) (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - NCC San Diego 12/2/89 (#396) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - National Centennial Celebration Revised (#396A) (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - John Kaplan Memorial 12/11/89 (#397) (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Bay Area Council Panel 1/26/90 (#398) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Darwin Lecture (K. Jackson) 1/30/90 (#399) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Ralston Award Welcome 1/30/90 (#400) (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - ICC-Mexico 2/10/90 (#401) (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Mexico ICC Welcoming Remarks 2/10/90 (#401A) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - On Approaching Big Problems St. Mary's 2/16/90 (#402) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Human Biology Reunion Notes 2/23-2/24/90 (#403A) (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Human Biology Reunion Darwin (#403B) (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - ICC Canada/Toronto 3/10/90 (#404) (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - PA Med. Foundation-The New Generation Gap 3/17/90(#405) (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Don't They Love Us Anymore? 3/19/90 (#406) (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Don't They Love Us Anymore? AGB-San Diego 3/19/90 (#406) (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Academic Council Address 4/5/90 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Intro of Paul Ehrlich 4/19/90 (#408) (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - In Praise of Mike Heyman April 1990 (#408A) (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Responsibility & the University-Tanner 4/26/90 (#409) (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Barton Class Lecture Notes 5/3/90 (#410) (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Rape Awareness Week Intro 5/14/90 (#411) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Mikhail Gorbachev Intro (not used) 6/4/90 (#412) (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - B Hillel Evening (notes) 6/5/90 (#412) (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Gorbachev Speech 6/4/90 (#412A) (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Commencement Welcome 6/17/90 (#413A) (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Commencement Farewell to Graduates 6/17/90 (#413B) (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Intro to Marian Wright Edelman 6/17/90 (#413C) (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Marian Wright Edelman Commencement Address 6/17/90 (#413D) (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - President's Forum AAHE Chicago 6/18-6/19/90 (#414) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Sierra Camp Presentation June 1990 (#415) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Sierra Camp Presentation June 1990 (#415) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - American Leadership Forum (notes) (#416) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - BoT Retreat, Fallen Leaf Lakes September 1990 (#417) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Tri-University Forum Welcome Remarks 9/13/90 (#418) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - GSB Welcome 9/18/90 (outline) (#420) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Welcome to Medical Students (notes) 9/12/90 (#419) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Transfers-RA's-Welcomes (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Parents Day Convocation 9/21/90 (#421) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - RA Welcome 1990 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Welcome to Freshmen 9/21/90 (#422) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Welcome to New Faculty 9/21/90 (#423) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Sophomore Celebration (notes) 9/25/90 (#424) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Senate-Stanford's Financial Situation 9/27/90 (#425A) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Senate Indirect Cost Recovery Statement (#425B) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Grad Student Convocation (notes) 9/30/90 See #238 (#426) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Junior Convocation Intro of Jim Gibbons 9/30/90 (#427A) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Jim Gibbon's Speech 9/30/90 (#427B) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Welcome Remarks Centennial Year Opening 9/30/90 (#428A) (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Intro of Mae Jemison 9/30/90 (#428B) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Intro of Vartan Gregorian 9/30/90 (#428C) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Opening Day Schedule 9/30/90 (#428D) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - SPEARfest remarks SLAC/SSRL10/1/90 (#429) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Class Reunions '40 10/12/90 (#430) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - After dinner remarks – Rockefeller Conf./Service Req. 10/17/90 (#431) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Child Care Community Message 10/27/90 (#432) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - NCC-Hong Kong 10/28/90 (#433) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Doing Better, Feeling Worse 11/12/90 (#434) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Robt. Hofstader Memorial – Stan. Commun. 11/26/90 (#435) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Remarks to Faculty Senate 11/28/90 (#435A) (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Pheonix Talk on Housing 1/10/91 (#436) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Welcome-Second Centennial Symposium (Berg) 1/11/91 (#437) (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Art Coladarci Memorial – Cubberly 1/28/91 (#438) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Preparing for a Different World – Dan Ayrault Memorial Seattle 2/2/91 (#439) (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Preparing for a Different World 2/2/91 (#439) (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Remarks to Stanford Alumni-WDC 2/19/91 (#440) (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - The University in Transition – Chicago Alumni 2/20/91 (#441) (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Parents' Day Convocation (notes) 3/9/91 (#442) (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - House (Indirect Costs) Testimony – Subcommittee on Oversight & Investigations 3/15/91 (#443) (Box 11, Folder 40)